(Howard:)But before I go...
(Howard:)...would you mind if I just take one picture
of us together for my Facebook page?
(Summer:)Sure.
(Penny:)Okay. Great.
(Howard:)Can I take one
where it looks like we're making out?
(Sheldon:)Okay, now you're going to insert
the flash drive into the USB port.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
(Sheldon:)She calls me Moon Pie
because I'm nummy-nummy...
(Sheldon:)...and she could just eat me up.
(Sheldon:)Now please put the flash drive
in the USB port.
(Sheldon:)The one that looks like
a little duck's mouth.
- Hey, how'd it go?
- Terminator broke my phone.
(Leonard:)Excuse me.
(Leonard:)Okay, I'll be honest with you.
I've spent the last two hours imagining
various scenarios in my head...
...trying to come up with some line
to say to you...
(Leonard:)...but then I finally realized
you're a human being, I'm a human being.
(Leonard:)I could just say...
CONDUCTOR [ON PA]:
Next stop, Santa Barbara.
(Summer:)I'm sorry. This is me.
"Hi, my name's Leonard."
(Sheldon:)So I'm thinking you won the Nobel Prize,
what, three years ago...
(Sheldon:)...so you must deal with a whole lot
of "What has Smoot done lately?"
(Sheldon:)My thought is we continue my research
as a team, you know...
(Sheldon:)...Cooper-Smoot, alphabetical...
(Sheldon:)...and when we win the Nobel Prize,
you'll be back on top.
(George Smoot:)With all due respect, Dr. Cooper,
are you on crack?
Fine. Smoot-Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Wow, what a diva.